<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Will-Ellwood.com</title>
    <link>www.will-ellwood.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Will-Ellwood.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Will Ellwood</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.will-ellwood.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/now/</guid>
      <description>As of September 23rd 2019:
 I have just moved to Aberdeen, Scotland I am looking to spend a lot more time writing prose and code for myself I am still listening to a lot of Earth  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m Will.
I wear many hats, but these are some of the things that I do:
 Write code Do things with Linux Play games Brew coffee Drink beer Take photographs, mostly of cats  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/talks/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Talks Past Talks DevOps Notts August 21st 2019 Held at Rebel Recruiters, Nottingham.
A talk and demonstration of Test Driven Infrastructure development using Molecule to control Docker, Ansible, TestInfra, and an assortment of linting tools.
Tech Nottingham July 9th 2018 Held at Antenna, Nottingham 18:30.
Everything is terrible. How can we change that? In this talk we will discuss how speculative fiction magazines can publish fiction &amp;amp; articles to a global audience in a way that is accountable to their readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 18:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/finally/</guid>
      <description>Finally!
I have finally finished a version of my site’s theme which I’m happy with. It isn’t anything special and it isn’t anything fancy, but it’s mine, so falls firmly into the if I break it I fix it way of things, which is exactly what I want this site.
The week I’d intended to spend working on the theme was interrupted by working on another site I manage and then week on-call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Delays</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/theme-delays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/theme-delays/</guid>
      <description>I made a mistake when creating this category of posts. It&#39;s stuck inside a branch I don&#39;t want to commit yet and can&#39;t really be bothered to untangle the mess of files. I&#39;m meant to be working on a new theme for this site and it is taking longer than anticipated because I only put the odd half hour or so in every few weeks.
The same pattern of occasional short bursts is true with my attempts at writing fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aberdeen I</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/aberdeen-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 12:01:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/aberdeen-i/</guid>
      <description>Last week I moved northwards to Aberdeen, Scotland. This has been on the cards for a couple of months now, ever since my partner was offered a job in the city. I had intended to write more about the move, but I didn&#39;t really have the capacity to until now.
The opportunity J has here is significant, so had to be taken, even if it means leaving behind the communities we were involved with, like the Speculators and Tech Nottingham.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granite City One</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/granite-city-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 19:56:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/granite-city-one/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m sat in The Distilling House, the bar past security at Aberdeen Airport. There&#39;s a last of a glass of Glen Garioch and the remains of a steak sandwich next to me. Jen &amp;amp; I have just visited the city for two nights so we could put boots on the ground here for the first time in five years. (This is our second visit.) She spent about three hours taking with colleagues at her new job, and we both looked at a house to rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barzun Process</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/barzun-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 15:20:27 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/barzun-process/</guid>
      <description>Another year, another short story published. This time the story is called Barzun Process and is available to purchase from Open Polyversity in Open Polyversity, which is available from their Lulu page.
Maybe I&#39;ll write some detailed notes about the story later, but it&#39;s a weird story for weird people about cyborgs &amp;amp; love. It massively inspired by narrative principles expound by the Nier: Automata director Yoko Taro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Signal</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/test-signal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 22:20:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/signal/test-signal/</guid>
      <description>The time is 22:23 on a Tuesday evening. I am sat on the sofa with a mug of &amp;ldquo;sleepy tea&amp;rdquo;. My cat has abandoned me for the comfort of the bed. Truly I am reaching middle age in the most pathetic way possible. And I&#39;m writing some sample content for a hidden section of my website instead of heading upstairs to join the cat because apparently this is more important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2018: The Year In Review</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/2018-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 17:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/2018-review/</guid>
      <description>Prelude For many of my friends 2018 was another cruel year. Personally, I survived without too much damage, but even still I&#39;m fearing 2019, with the threat of a cliff edge Brexit coming a decade after the financial crash which ruined my twenties. Still, we cannot change the past and Brexit, along with other upcoming political disasters, are existential problems, so let us instead review the moments of 2018.
The Good   I attend Hack24 in March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 35, 2018</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/week35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:40:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/week35/</guid>
      <description>Everything is awful. Our planet and societies are facing numerous ecological collapses inflicted by humanity. There’s no escape in the face of post-capitalism flattening all cultural consumption into a desert of mega-franchises. All we can do is record our activities and perceptions in the desperate hope of being able to reconstruct the a place outside of what Alexei Yurchak called “HyperNormalisation”. This is my attempt for week 35, 2018.
Status &amp;amp; Plan (Monday)  It is a bank holiday weekend here in the UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEVIL&#39;S FOOL</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/devils/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 21:24:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/devils/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this far later than intended because life interrupted. On July 9th I gave a talk at Tech Nottingham called “Small Steps To A Better World: Content Warnings And Socially Responsible Practice”. There is an abstract on the talks page of this site, but the quick summary is the implementation of trigger warnings at Strange Horizons and why people in tech should be good people. The talk went well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMALL STEPS TO A BETTER WORLD</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/small-steps-better-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 17:05:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/small-steps-better-world/</guid>
      <description>I have worked in Nottingham for almost two years. Due to that, I have been able to attend events organised by Tech Nottingham. Tech Nottingham is a community organisation run by Andrew &amp;amp; Emma Seward, with the mission of making Nottingham a better place to live, and to work in technology. As part of that, they organise and facilitate events each month, ranging from Women in Tech to a breakfast event called Tech on Toast (which starts at a time in the morning far too ungodly for a commuter from Leicester to attend).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>44 Fields</title>
      <link>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/44-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.will-ellwood.com/posts/44-fields/</guid>
      <description>My short story 44 Fields is now available to read at Big Echo. You can read it here.
If you are interested I have collected a few thoughts here:
  The opening image of a field of barley derives from the Ken Loach film &amp;ldquo;The Wind that Shakes the Barley&amp;rdquo; and my defuse memories of watching it almost a decade ago. Other films that come to mind with long grasses and war include Gladiator and The Thin Red Line.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>