<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Will-Ellwood.com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Will-Ellwood.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2018 - Will Ellwood</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Will.
I wear many hats, but these are some of the things that I do:
 Write code Do things with Linux Play games Brew coffee Drink beer Take photographs, mostly of cats  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Talks Tech Nottingham July 9th 2018 Held at Antenna, Nottingham 18:30.
Everything is terrible. How can we change that? In this talk we will discuss how speculative fiction magazines can publish fiction &amp;amp; articles to a global audience in a way that is accountable to their readers.
We will also discuss ways in which we can look at and implement policies and technologies which allow us to be technologists who are accountable for the harm their work may cause and posses the tools to slow the emergence of what the writer Bruce Sterling calls the &amp;ldquo;Gothic Hi-Tech&amp;rdquo;; a world in which technology is brilliant but everything is dying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SMALL STEPS TO A BETTER WORLD</title>
      <link>/posts/small-steps-better-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 17:05:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/small-steps-better-world/</guid>
      <description>I have worked in Nottingham for almost two years. Due to that, I have been able to attend events organised by Tech Nottingham. Tech Nottingham is a community organisation run by Andrew &amp;amp; Emma Seward, with the mission of making Nottingham a better place to live, and to work in technology. As part of that, they organise and facilitate events each month, ranging from Women in Tech to a breakfast event called Tech on Toast (which starts at a time in the morning far too ungodly for a commuter from Leicester to attend).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>44 Fields</title>
      <link>/posts/44-fields/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/44-fields/</guid>
      <description>My short story 44 Fields is now available to read at Big Echo. You can read it here.
If you are interested I have collected a few thoughts here:
 The opening image of a field of barley derives from the Ken Loach film &amp;ldquo;The Wind that Shakes the Barley&amp;rdquo; and my defuse memories of watching it almost a decade ago. Other films that come to mind with long grasses and war include Gladiator and The Thin Red Line.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>