<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pages on Will-Ellwood.com</title>
    <link>/categories/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pages on Will-Ellwood.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Will Ellwood</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Log</title>
      <link>/log/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/log/</guid>
      <description>2 - 2020-01-27 - Glen Garroch
Tonight I split the final 10% of my bottle of Glen Garroch with Jen. There&#39;s no more whiskey left in the house, but it had to be done as it would have spoiled if not drank. Honest!
1 - 2020-01-21 - Beeston - Fourth Night
I&#39;ve been on the road since Friday evening, and walked the length of the Malverns, climbed many indoor boulder problems in two different cities, slept in three different beds, and now just want to go home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 17:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;now page&amp;rdquo;, and I think they are a good idea.
As of January 1st 2020:
 I am getting used to working remotely such that it&#39;s now normal for me I have started rock climbing indoors again and am planning some easy adventures for the spring  As of September 23rd 2019:
 I have just moved to Aberdeen, Scotland I am looking to spend a lot more time writing prose and code for myself I am still listening to a lot of Earth  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&#39;m Will.
I wear many hats, but these are some of the things that I do:
 Write code Do things with Linux Play games Brew coffee Drink beer Take photographs, mostly of cats  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Talks Aberdeen Python User&#39;s Group January 8th 2020 Poetry in Python Held at Code Base One, Aberdeen.
An introduction to Poetry, a Python tool to manage packaing and dependecy management that is really quite beautiful.
Past Talks DevOps Notts August 21st 2019 Test Driven Infrastructure with Molecule Held at Rebel Recruiters, Nottingham.
A talk and demonstration of Test Driven Infrastructure development using Molecule to control Docker, Ansible, TestInfra, and an assortment of linting tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>