<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hidden-signals on Will-Ellwood.com</title>
    <link>/hidden-signal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hidden-signals on Will-Ellwood.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019 - Will Ellwood</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:43:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/hidden-signal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020 02 11</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/2020-02-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/2020-02-11/</guid>
      <description>The sun is setting and I have been toiling away doing some tasks which should be automated for the #dayjob. In about half an hour I&#39;m heading to my local climbing wall to see what they have planned for the year. I don&#39;t know what to expect from Transition Extreme since I&#39;m a relatively new customer of theirs, but I&#39;d like to see the bouldering area enlarged.
One of my fingers slightly hurts from a finger board session on Sunday, so I won&#39;t be climbing tonight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glen Garroch</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/glen-garroch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 18:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/glen-garroch/</guid>
      <description>Tonight I split the final 10% of my bottle of Glen Garroch with Jen. There&#39;s no more whiskey left in the house, but it had to be done as it would have spoiled if not drank. Honest!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beeston - Fourth Night</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/beeston-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 21:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/beeston-nights/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been on the road since Friday evening, and walked the length of the Malverns, climbed many indoor boulder problems in two different cities, slept in three different beds, and now just want to go home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Year 2020</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/new-year-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 15:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/new-year-2020/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year!
Thank God the old year is over.
I do not intend to write a end of year wrap up as I did last year. Public reflection isn&#39;t a genre of writing I enjoy contributing to even if I&#39;m a happy voyer of other&#39;s contributions, so this post, as reflective as it is, is in my semi-secret feed.
So last year:
 I didn&#39;t like the UK election results one bit and I&#39;m not hopeful for the future I moved to Scotland I started working as a remote first employee I briefly fell out of love to varying degrees with writing anything either code or prose I started rock climbing again and rediscovered a central metaphor in my life In the last couple of weeks of the year I started free-writing on a daily basis again  I can&#39;t predict what will happen in the coming year, but I can describe some aspirations:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/finally/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 18:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/finally/</guid>
      <description>Finally!
I have finally finished a version of my site’s theme which I’m happy with. It isn’t anything special and it isn’t anything fancy, but it’s mine, so falls firmly into the if I break it I fix it way of things, which is exactly what I want this site.
The week I’d intended to spend working on the theme was interrupted by working on another site I manage and then week on-call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Delays</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/theme-delays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/theme-delays/</guid>
      <description>I made a mistake when creating this category of posts. It&#39;s stuck inside a branch I don&#39;t want to commit yet and can&#39;t really be bothered to untangle the mess of files. I&#39;m meant to be working on a new theme for this site and it is taking longer than anticipated because I only put the odd half hour or so in every few weeks.
The same pattern of occasional short bursts is true with my attempts at writing fiction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Granite City One</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/granite-city-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 19:56:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/granite-city-one/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m sat in The Distilling House, the bar past security at Aberdeen Airport. There&#39;s a last of a glass of Glen Garioch and the remains of a steak sandwich next to me. Jen &amp;amp; I have just visited the city for two nights so we could put boots on the ground here for the first time in five years. (This is our second visit.) She spent about three hours taking with colleagues at her new job, and we both looked at a house to rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Signal</title>
      <link>/hidden-signal/test-signal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 22:20:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hidden-signal/test-signal/</guid>
      <description>The time is 22:23 on a Tuesday evening. I am sat on the sofa with a mug of &amp;ldquo;sleepy tea&amp;rdquo;. My cat has abandoned me for the comfort of the bed. Truly I am reaching middle age in the most pathetic way possible. And I&#39;m writing some sample content for a hidden section of my website instead of heading upstairs to join the cat because apparently this is more important.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>